<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[KIDS ZONE DAYCARE]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[KIDS ZONE DAYCARE]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/kids-zone-day-care/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 22:43:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/kids-zone-day-care/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="http://www.kzdaycare.com/P5044918_800x600.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>http://www.kzdaycare.com/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">efe0ee2d-36bc-4b0b-9024-2e03ea7d60ff</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 22:18:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>A Licensed DayCare Center!  What are the advantages of daycare centers?  Many parents like daycare centers because they offer a formal, structured environment. All daycare centers are inspected for licensing purposes, caregivers are supervised (many classrooms have more than one teacher), and a director oversees the entire operation. Another plus: Centers have clearcut rules for parents to follow (such as pickup and drop-off times) so you know exactly what is expected of you.  Also, the arrangement is more stable (compared to, say, nanny or relative care) because the center agrees to watch over your child regardless whether a teacher is sick or tardy or even tired of working for you.  Staff members at good centers are trained in early childhood education so they know what to expect from your child developmentally and are able to nurture his growing skills accordingly. If the center you're considering doesn't hire knowledgeable staff, keep looking.   Good daycare centers include a nice mix of activities during the day to teach different skills, such as singing, dancing, and storytelling. "They're not just playing all day they're learning new things." Many of the instructional projects are a good mix of left- and right-brain activities, usually made of simple objects like blocks or beans or vinyl letters for creativity, but presented in an organized, structured, and methodical way. Ongoing research by the National Institute of Child Health and Human Development suggests that children in quality daycare centers may even have an intellectual edge over those in other kinds of care. When researchers compared kids in quality daycare to those in other, equally high-quality childcare situations, children in centers performed a little better on tests. Finally, toddlers can benefit from the chance to socialize with other children, which they may not get to do as often or at all when a nanny or a relative cares for them at home.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kids-zone-day-care/a-licensed-daycare-center-what-are-the-advantages-of-dayca/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ac3478fa-25ef-4566-a2a1-b1b155587dba</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 22:43:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kids Zone Day Care]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Kids Zone Day Care</h1><p>4500 S. Business US-27, Saint Johns, Mi. 48879</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.kzdaycare.com/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">95cc1455-665d-49d8-8467-8dd16d801b6d</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 22:18:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Kids Zone DayCare was founded in 1994 by Linda Parr and Judy Kleinjans.  </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.kzdaycare.com/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">92c15a22-c190-4b03-a7a6-1ccd34d8da92</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 22:22:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are located on Business US-27 South of St. Johns, Michigan </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.kzdaycare.com/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0e710431-fcd0-4ef5-a817-f60879014bba</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 22:28:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>